 
One Liner Jokes 
1. I can’t believe I got fired from the calendar factory: all I did was take a day off! 
2. Money talks: mine always says is goodbye. 
3. I went to see the doctor about my short-term memory problems — the first thing he did 
was make me pay in advance. 
4. You have two parts of the brain, “left” and “right” — in the left side, there’s nothing right 
and in the right side, there’s nothing left. 
5. Why do bees hum? They don’t remember the lyrics! 
6. I have a dog to provide me with unconditional love, but I also have a cat to remind me 
that I don’t deserve it: it’s all about balance. 
7. Don’t spell part backwards. It’s a trap. 
8. Today a man knocked on my door and asked for a small donation towards the local 
swimming pool. I gave him a glass of water. 
9. Most people are shocked when they find out how bad I am as an electrician. 
10. I find it ironic that the colors red, white, and blue stand for freedom until they are flashing 
behind you. 
11. Don’t trust atoms, they make up everything. 
12. Thanks for explaining the word “many” to me, it means a lot. 
13. I hope when I inevitably choke to death on gummy bears people just say I was killed by 
bears and leave it at that. 
14. I accidentally handed my wife a glue stick instead of a Chapstick. She still isn’t talking to 
me. 
15. I’m reading a book about anti-gravity. It’s impossible to put down. 
16. I wasn’t originally going to get a brain transplant, but then I changed my mind. 
17. R.I.P boiled water. You will be mist. 
18. I got a new pair of gloves today, but they’re both ‘lefts’ which, on the one hand, is great, 
but on the other, it’s just not right. 
19. My wife just found out I replaced our bed with a trampoline; she hit the roof. 
20. What is the best thing about living in Switzerland? Well, the flag is a big plus. 
﻿ 
One Liner Jokes 
21. Did you hear about the guy who got hit in the head with a can of soda? He didn’t get hurt 
because it was a soft drink. 
22. The future, the present and the past walked into a bar. Things got a little tense. 
23. At what age is it appropriate to tell my dog that he’s adopted? 
24. I just found out I’m colorblind. The diagnosis came completely out of the purple. 
25. I bought some shoes from a drug dealer. I don’t know what he laced them with, but I’ve 
been tripping all day. 
26. My boss is going to fire the employee with the worst posture. I have a hunch, it might be 
me. 
27. I started out with nothing, and I still have most of it. 
28. Smoking will kill you… Bacon will kill you… And yet, smoking bacon will cure it. 
29. I was addicted to the hokey pokey… but thankfully, I turned myself around. 
30. The Man Who Created Autocorrect Has Died. Restaurant In Peace. 
31. I used to think I was indecisive, but now I’m not too sure. 
32. My wife likes it when I blow air on her when she’s hot, but honestly… I’m not a fan. 
33. The first time I got a universal remote control I thought to myself, “This changes 
everything”. 
34. I refused to believe my father, the road worker, was stealing from his job, but when I got 
home all the signs were there. 
35. I recently decided to sell my vacuum cleaner — all it was doing was gathering dust. 
36. Where there’s a will, there’s a relative. 
37. It’s hard to explain puns to kleptomaniacs — they’re always taking things literally. 
38. I like to hold hands at the movies… which always seems to startle strangers. 
39. There are three kinds of people: those who can count and those who can’t. 
40. Whenever I lose my TV controller, I always find it at a remote location. 
41. My first job was working in an orange juice factory, but I got canned: I just couldn’t 
concentrate. 
42. My math teacher called me average — it’s so mean! 
﻿ 
One Liner Jokes 
43. I don’t have an attitude problem. You have a perception problem. 
44. I’m skeptical of anyone who tells me they do yoga every day — that’s a bit of a stretch. 
45. “The worst time to have a heart attack is during a game of charades.” – Demetri Martin 
46. “The New England Journal of Medicine reports that 9 out of 10 doctors agree that 1 out 
of 10 doctors is an idiot.” – Jay Leno 
47. “I have a lot of growing up to do. I realized that the other day inside my fort.” – Zach 
Galifianakis 
48. “Honesty may be the best policy, but it’s important to remember that apparently, by 
elimination, dishonesty is the second-best policy.” – George Carlin 
49. “I looked up my family tree and found out I was the sap.” – Rodney Dangerfield 
50. Keep the dream alive — hit your snooze button. 
51. “My therapist says I have a preoccupation with vengeance. We’ll see about that.” – 
Stewart Francis 
52. I was wondering why the ball kept getting bigger and bigger, and then it hit me. 
53. The person who invented knock knock jokes should get a no bell prize. 
54. The other day I asked the banker to check my balance, so she pushed me. 
55. For a while, Houdini would use a trap door in every single one of his show – I guess you 
could say it was a stage he was going through. 
56. I hope there’s no pop quiz at the class trip to the Coca Cola factory. 
57. I didn’t like my beard at first, but it grew on me. 
58. A baseball walks into a bar —  the bartender throws it out. 
59. I doubt, therefore I might be. 
60. I used to have a handle on life, but then it broke. 
61. I had an “hour-glass” figure, but then the sand shifted. 
62. When everything is coming your way — you’re in the wrong lane. 
63. “Crime in multi-story car parks. That is wrong on so many different levels.” — Tim Vine 
64. “I was raised as an only child, which really annoyed my sister.” —Will Marsh 
﻿ 
One Liner Jokes 
65. “People who use selfie sticks really need to have a good, long look at themselves.” — Abi 
Roberts 
66. “A thesaurus is great. There’s no other word for it” —Ross Smith 
67. “I failed math so many times at school I can’t even count.” — Stewart Francis 
68. “I saw a documentary on how ships are kept together. Riveting!” — Stewart Francis 
69. I once saw two people wrapped in a barcode and had to ask — “are you an item?” 
70. I went to buy camouflage trousers, but I couldn’t find any. 
71. My husband and I were happy for 20 years. And then we met. 
72. I, for one, like Roman numerals. 
73. When my boss asked me who was stupid, me or him, I told him he doesn’t hire stupid 
people. 
74. Any married person should forget their mistakes. No use for two people remembering 
the same thing. 
 
